innovateus.net 2016-03-14

# Privacy Policy

Thank you for choosing InnovateUs.Net.

InnovateUs.Net, Inc. ("InnovateUs.Net") recognizes that its customers, visitors, users, and others who use [www.InnovateUs.Net](http://www.innovateus.net/ "www.InnovateUs.Net") or other web sites owned or operated by InnovateUs.Net (the "InnovateUs.Net Sites") (collectively or individually "Users") value their privacy. This Privacy Notice details important information regarding the use and disclosure of User information collected on the InnovateUs.Net Sites. InnovateUs.Net provides this Privacy Notice to help you make an informed decision about whether to use or continue using the InnovateUs.Net Sites.

This Privacy Notice is incorporated into and is subject to the InnovateUs.Net Terms of Use. Your use of the InnovateUs.Net Sites and any personal information you provide on the InnovateUs.Net Sites remains subject to the terms of this Privacy Notice and our Terms of Use.

Please note that any video, image, or other content posted at the direction of Users onto the InnovateUs.Net Sites becomes published content and is not considered personally identifiable information subject to this Privacy Notice.

* We provide personally identifiable information and non-personally-identifiable information to our subsidiaries, affiliated companies, or other businesses or persons for the purpose of processing such information on our behalf. We require that these parties agree to process such information in compliance with our privacy policy, and we use reasonable efforts to limit their use of such information and to use other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.
* We do not share your personally identifiable information (such as name or email address) with other, third-party companies for their commercial or marketing use without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out. 
* We do share non-personally-identifiable information (such as anonymous User usage data, referring / exit pages and URLs, platform types, number of clicks, etc.) with interested third-parties to assist them in understanding the usage patterns for certain content, services, advertisements, promotions, and/or functionality on the InnovateUs.Net Sites.
* We may release personally identifiable information and/or non-personally-identifiable information if required to do so by law, or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with state and federal laws (such as U.S. Copyright Law) or respond to a court order, subpoena, or search warrant.
* InnovateUs.Net also reserves the right to disclose personally identifiable information and/or non-personally-identifiable information that InnovateUs.Net believes, in good faith, is appropriate or necessary to enforce our Terms of Use, take precautions against liability, to investigate and defend itself against any third-party claims or allegations, to assist government enforcement agencies, to protect the security or integrity of our web site, and to protect the rights, property, or personal safety of InnovateUs.Net, our Users or others.

### Your Choices

You may, of course, decline to submit personally identifiable information through the InnovateUs.Net Sites, in which case InnovateUs.Net may not be able to provide certain services to you. You may update or correct your personal profile information and email preferences at any time by visiting your account profile page. Please note that media files uploaded by Users to the InnovateUs.Net Sites cannot be removed and remain subject to our Terms of Use.

To protect your privacy and security, we take reasonable steps (such as requesting a unique password) to verify your identity before granting you profile access or making corrections. You are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your unique password and account information at all times.

Please contact InnovateUs.Net with any questions or comments about this Privacy Notice, your personal information, your consent, or your opt-in or opt-out choices using this contact form. Third-party Advertisers, Links to Other Sites

InnovateUs.Net allows other companies, called third-party ad servers or ad networks, to serve advertisements within the InnovateUs.Net Sites. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to send, directly to your browser, the advertisements and links that appear on the InnovateUs.Net Sites. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They may also use other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize the advertising content you see.

InnovateUs.Net does not provide any personally identifiable information to these third-party ad servers or ad networks without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out. However, please note that if an advertiser asks InnovateUs.Net to show an advertisement to a certain audience (for example, men ages 18-34) or audience segment (for example, men ages 18-24 who have viewed certain channels of content) and you respond to that advertisement, the advertiser or ad-server may conclude that you fit the description of the audience they are trying to reach. The advertiser may also use information regarding your use of the InnovateUs.Net Sites, such as the number of times you viewed an ad (but not any personally identifiable information), to determine which ads to deliver to you.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers or ad networks (see links below) for more information on their practices and for instructions on how to opt-out of certain practices. InnovateUs.Net's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

### Our Commitment To Data Security

InnovateUs.Net uses commercially reasonable physical, managerial, and technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of your personal information. We cannot, however, ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to InnovateUs.Net and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission of information, InnovateUs.Net makes commercially reasonable efforts to ensure the security of our systems. However, please note that this is not a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards.

If InnovateUs.Net learns of a security systems breach, then we may attempt to notify you electronically so that you can take appropriate protective steps. InnovateUs.Net may post a notice on the InnovateUs.Net Sites if a security breach occurs. Depending on where you live, you may have a legal right to receive notice of a security breach in writing. To receive a free written notice of a security breach (or to withdraw your consent from receiving electronic notice) you should notify us using this contact form.

### Our Commitment To Childrens' Privacy

Protecting the privacy of young children is especially important. For that reason, InnovateUs.Net does not knowingly collect or maintain personally identifiable information or non-personally-identifiable information on the InnovateUs.Net Sites from persons under 18 years of age, and no part of our website is directed to persons under 18. If you are under 18 years of age, then please do not use or access the InnovateUs.Net Sites at any time or in any manner. If InnovateUs.Net learns that personally identifiable information of persons under 18 years of age has been collected on the InnovateUs.Net Sites without verified parental consent, then InnovateUs.Net will take the appropriate steps to delete this information.

### Special Note to International Users

The InnovateUs.Net Sites are hosted in the United States and are intended for and directed to Users in the United States. If you are a User accessing the InnovateUs.Net Sites from the European Union, Asia, or any other region with laws or regulations governing personal data collection, use, and disclosure, that differ from United States laws, please be advised that through your continued use of the InnovateUs.Net Sites, which are governed by U.S. law, this Privacy Notice, and our Terms of Use, you are transferring your personal information to the United States and you consent to that transfer.

### In the Event of Merger, Sale, or Bankruptcy

In the event that InnovateUs.Net is acquired by or merged with a third party entity, we reserve the right, in any of these circumstances, to transfer or assign the information we have collected from our Users as part of such merger, acquisition, sale, or other change of control. In the unlikely event of our bankruptcy, insolvency, reorganization, receivership, or assignment for the benefit of creditors, or the application of laws or equitable principles affecting creditors' rights generally, we may not be able to control how your personal information is treated, transferred, or used.

### Changes and updates to this Privacy Notice

This Privacy Notice may be revised periodically and this will be reflected by the "effective date" below. Please revisit this page to stay aware of any changes. In general, we only use your personal information in the manner described in the Privacy Notice in effect when we received the personal information you provided. Your continued use of the InnovateUs.Net Sites constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Notice and any future revisions.

For revisions to this Privacy Notice that may be materially less restrictive on our use or disclosure of the personal information you have already provided to us, we will attempt to obtain your consent before implementing such revisions with respect to such information.

### Contact Information:

Please contact InnovateUs.Net with any questions or comments about this Privacy Notice using this contact form.
